<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Pankaj Mishra</title>
		<description>Personal blog</description>		
		<link>http://localhost:4000</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Google Summer of Code - Blog #0!</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Hey there. Welcome to my first blog of an upcoming series of blogs where I will be trying to chronicle my journey this year as an open source contributor to RADIS under the Google Summer of Code program!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-p&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 23:34:56 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/gsoc/gsoc-blog-0</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/gsoc/gsoc-blog-0</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Introducing a new blog!</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Hi all. This is a new blog post which is primarily meant to test how to go about writing new posts for this blog which I very
conveniently lifted off of some github repository. Regardless, this is an excellent light-weight theme, and to be honest I like
it so much it almost feels like I commissioned it. So I think the first thank you goes to the awesome creators of this beautiful 
theme, which I found out are a bunch (or possibly a lonewolf) web developer based out of Bangalore. So thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from the credits, this will also serve as a practise for formatting these posts using a code editor. For refernce, I am writing
this as a markdown file in VS Code and thus have no idea how this actually looks on the web. I’ll try out a couple of markdown
commands to just make sure I got the hang of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;headings&quot;&gt;Headings&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Under this, I would like to have multiple subheadings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;topic-1&quot;&gt;Topic 1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this should ideally be a subparagraph under the above heading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;topic-2&quot;&gt;Topic 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second subtopic.
Trying to insert a link as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/pkjm&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;. Heck I gotta say VS Code is beautiful. Even with markdown, it knows just the right type of syntax highlighting to help me out without making it look like a rainbow (&lt;em&gt;cough&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;cough&lt;/em&gt; eclipse.. &lt;em&gt;cough&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;topic-3&quot;&gt;Topic 3&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the last subheading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this should suffice for a blog post. For all those unfortunate enough to have read this whole thing up until this point, you have my sincerest condolences and a genuine feeling of appreciation from the bottom of my heart. Now please dont do that again. Ciao.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-p&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 23:34:56 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/personal/new-blog</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/personal/new-blog</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>